(Bernadette:)What kind of comics do the guys like?
(Stuart:)Um, a little bit of everything.
Mostly superhero stuff.
- All right, well, who's the best superhero?
- Shh!
(Stuart:)You can't ask a question like that in here.
Are you trying to start a rumble?
Well, what do you recommend?
(Stuart:)Well, uh, let's see, you've got your basic
clean-cut good guys:
(Stuart:)Superman, Spider-Man, Captain America.
Then you have your darker anti-heroes:
(Stuart:)Your Batman, your Wolverine, Punisher.
(Amy:)Ooh, I do love a bad boy.
(Penny:)As evidenced by your boyfriend
and his fear of hamsters.
(Sheldon:)If I were you,
I'd go for Fables number one.
(Stuart:)Artwork is sophisticated,
it's intelligently written...
(Stuart:)...and it doesn't objectify...
(Stuart:)...or stereotype women.
- Oh, Thor. He's hot.
(Stuart:)Yeah, he kind of is.
(Raj:)And we're blending...
(Raj:)...and we're blending, and we're done.